I will never forget you that day
I have feelings that transcend time
I want to see you right now
Your voice is great, isn't it? It's amazing.
There were many things you had to work hard for after becoming an idol,
Did you have confidence that you would not fail?
Yes, I did. Yes, I did.
When I thought about what to do after quitting the agency,
I knew I wanted to become an idol,
At that time, I looked into it and found that it was an audition during an encounter,
I wasn't very confident in that act,
I thought if I could call this my color, I could be the model who could cut the wall I wanted to be,
I decided to give it a try. What was your staff's challenge?
I was ~.
On a morning when the horizon glows
Your hope crumbles and crumbles
To the shards blown by the wind
Someone is muttering beautiful, this time why this audition was held at the right time,
Because I was really attracted by the concept.
Yes, thank you.
I wanted to buy such an automatic.
I couldn't.
Not at all. It would get in the way.
I think I heard that it's online tax free...half, was it?
Quarter. Like American.
Your father is American?
My grandfather is American.
My grandfather is American. When did you decide you wanted to be an idol?
When I was in elementary school. My older sister liked idols, so I was influenced by her.
I went to a concert and was completely influenced by her, so I decided to pursue it.
I was healed by other wedding corners,
I think I was healed in response to the other wedding corners...
Why? Why?
You were a little worried?
Yeah.
I mean...
Thank you. I've got it in my chest.
I realized something I wanted to tell you.
Thank you. Just a little bit.
I felt like I could be honest with you.
May I ask why you chose to audition for this show?
Tsu-san and a lot of other people were along the lines of the members who were chosen,
I heard that you wanted to create such an idol group,
I thought that this audition would be a good opportunity,
I thought that this audition would be a good opportunity for the Japanese idol community to participate,
I thought that this audition would be a good opportunity for the Japanese idol community to participate in this project.
Do you have a point that you can't lose to anyone else? I have a point that I can't lose to anyone.
I think I can't lose to anyone in my favorite dance and song practice.
You can't read the lyrics anymore because of your expression?
Reading out the lyrics
I want to do what we do, I'm sorry, what happened? I don't know where I'm going to get to.
I don't know, I just hang on to it
I'm so burnt out in my heart that I drown out my daily anxieties
I can't get rid of the longing
I thought that if I didn't act, I wouldn't change
At first, I didn't know what to do about this audition,
I've always liked Sue, and I've been following her on Twitter,
I was thinking what to do at first, but I have always liked Sue and watched her Twitter and so on.
I was thinking about what to do at first, but I have liked Sue for a long time and watched her Twitter,
I thought that was a good opportunity for me to apply.
I see. Thank you very much.
I hope you enjoy Juice-Juice's activities.
Thank you very much.
Have a stress-free time.
I'll do my best.
Are you okay? I'm totally fine.
Reach out to me.
I'm dreaming, I'm breathing, I'm eating, and you're here.
I love all of it, no matter how obvious or mean you are.
I thought this group was a great new experiment,
I was also attracted to the word "fuka," of course, but most of all I want to change myself,
But most of all, I want to change myself.
What do you want to change?
Every time I get to a certain point, I think that I am no longer as good as I was before, and I move on to something else.
If I join this group, I would like to change that first and foremost.
If I get into this group, I want to change that first, and if I get into this group, I want to do my best to make this the only place I want to be.
Q. I think your dancing is really beautiful, especially the way you can start and stop.
Q. I think your dancing is really beautiful, especially that you've already got the moves.
No, I haven't. But I don't think I'm bad at it.
But do you feel that you are not good at it?
Well, I am good at ballads and not so good at fast-paced songs,
I see.
Do you have a lot of experience in auditioning for Korean groups?
Have you ever auditioned in Japan?
This is my first time.
I see.
I had actually given up on auditioning.
I like Psy-Sy's music, and when I heard you were going to do it
When I heard you were going to do it
I thought I would give it one last try, so I applied.
Thank you very much.
It was the first time for me to sing out loud for so long... to hold hands... to be warm... to be alone... to hate... to be alone.
If you hate it, you'll be alone
Make your idol dreams come true
idol's dream come true super formula super formula super formula
Super Formula
I knew that when I decided to audition based on who I wanted to follow
I saw the interview with Sue. So I accepted.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Superformula.
Try one.
I wanted you to see it. My mind is chattering.
Please do.
Yes, yes, Hi everyone, welcome to our first Instagram live.We are all trainers of NFT Idol House Project.
Tanpan! Thank you!
I want to do my best! I have to work harder! I think.
you